http://www.perc.org/privacy-policy/

Home > Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us, and so we’ve prepared this document to explain what data we gather, how we use it, and how we strive to protect it. This privacy policy applies specifically to perc.org.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our Site, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available to you on our Site. You may be asked for identifying information such as name, email address, or mailing address. You certainly do not have to provide that information, and can browse our Site anonymously. But providing it helps us to keep you informed about our work, and helps us make sure our website is relevant and useful to you. Occasionally we may require that you provide a name, email or mailing address to access reports or other proprietary information.
Non-personal identification information
We collect non-personal identification information about those who interact with our Site, such as their browser name, the type of computer and technical information they are using to connect to our Site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information. This data is aggregated and used to help us make our Site stable and usable to all visitors.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and to store your preferences. Cookies can be helpful in customizing your website visit, and in helping us understand what types of information are most useful to our Site visitors. You always have the choice to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to provide an alert when cookies are being sent. If you do so, some parts of our Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
We use the personal information we collect to:
Run and operate a website that is useful and relevant
Display content on the Site correctly
Run a promotion, contest, survey or other website feature
Send you information about topics you have told us you care about
Update you on the impact of PERC via regular emails (which you will always have the option to unsubscribe from)
Respond to inquiries about our Site or programs
How we protect your information
We follow data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures designed to protect your information against unauthorized access or uses.
Sharing your personal information
We may selectively share our contact lists with like-minded allies who we think have information you would want to see. However, you can always request that your information not be shared with anyone by calling us at 406-587-9591 or emailing us at perc@perc.org. We also may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Changes to this privacy policy
PERC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at perc@perc.org.
×
Connect
Sign up to receive our updates and biannual magazine
Name*
Email
PhoneOrganizationCountryUnited StatesAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiNorth KoreaSouth KoreaKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMauritaniaMauritiusMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSaint MartinSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSudanSudan, SouthSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.YemenZambiaZimbabweAddress
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
Interests
Private Land Conservation and Agriculture
Wildlife Management and Conservation
Public Lands
Forest Policy
Water Markets
Oceans and Ocean Fisheries
Carbon and Climate Issues
Energy Policy
American Indian Policy
Free Market Environmentalism
Other related interestsOtherHow did you hear about PERC?Conference or EventEmailSocial MediaInternet SearchFellowship/ProgramOther OrganizationPERC PublicationPERC ReportsReferralCAPTCHA
